Where Peachtree Meets Sweet Auburn research files and interviews, 1991-1996
Emory University
- Audiovisual, 1991-1995, 1999, Series 4; Boxes 21-26, CD1-2
  - Audio cassettes, Subseries 4.1; Boxes 21-25
    - Clement, Josephine, October 19, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Dannals, Charles, August 8, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Darnell, Emma, September 29, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Dobbs, John Wesley, Funeral Service (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Dobbs, Mattiwilda, November 27, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Dobbs, Mattiwilda, Tape 1, November 11, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Dobbs, Mattiwilda, Tape 2, November 11, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Dodd, Marie, September 28, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Eaves, A. Reginald, Tape 1, November 11, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Eaves, A. Reginald, Tape 2, November 11, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Fowler, Wyche, August 15, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Fowlkes, William, June 4, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Fowlkes, William, Copy, June 4, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Franklin, David, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Franklin, David, Tape 1, September 14, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Franklin, David, Tape 2, September 14, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Franklin, Shirley, July 21, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Fuster, Angelo, April 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Gellerstedt, Larry, Jr., March 22, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Gellerstedt, Larry, III, September 28, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Glenn, Jack, June 1, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Gloster, Hugh, September 29, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Goldberg, Joel, September 29, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Granger, Paula, February 9, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Groover, D., March 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Head, John, February 2, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Henderson, Jacob and Freddie, September 16, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Hirthler, George, April 12, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Holder, Bob, Tape 1, March 2, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Holder, Bob, Tape 2, March 2, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Holloway, Jenelsie Walden. November 19, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Hollowell, Donald, July 6, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Brooke, February 5, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, July 27, 1991 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, July 29, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, March 11, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, May 2, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Jackson, Maynard, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Jackson, Maynard, Tape 2, September 9, 1991 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Jackson, Maynard, "Car Tour," Tape 1, February 2, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Jackson, Maynard, "Car Tour," Tape 2, February 2, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Jackson, Maynard, Speech, June 9, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Jackson, Maynard, November 29, 1994 [1] [Transcript available] [digitized; filename 3656-3657] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Jackson, Maynard, November 29, 1994 [2] [Transcript available] [digitized; filename 3658] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Jackson, Maynard, February 14, 1995 [Transcript available] [digitized; filename 3659-3660] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Jackson, Maynard, August 12, 1995 [1] [Transcript available] [digitized; filename 3661-3662] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Jackson, Maynard, August 12, 1995 [2] [Transcript available] [digitized; filename 3663-3664] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Jackson, Maynard, August 12, 1995 [3] [Transcript available] [digitized; filename 3665] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Johnson, Leroy, August 9, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Johnson, Leroy, September 12, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Jones, E. Ladd, October 5, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Jordan, Vernon, August 23, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Jordan, Windsor, November 28, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Kasten, Stan, "for AJC [ Atlanta Journal Constitution]," 1988 or 1989. (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - King, Coretta Scott, July 22, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - King, Lonnie, Tape 1, December 28, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - King, Lonnie, Tape 2, December 28, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - King, Martin Luther, III, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - King, Martin Luther, III, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Lokey, Hamilton, November 7, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Lomax, Michael, January 28, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Lowance, Mason, October 24, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Maddox, Lester, Tape 1, June 9, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Maddox, Lester, Tape 2, June 9, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Maddox, Lester, Tape 1, Copy, June 9, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Maddox, Lester, Tape 2, Copy, June 9, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Massell, Sam, September 10, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Massell, Sam, August 18, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - McGill, Ralph, Jr., February 8, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - McQueen, Neal, June 23, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Miller, Carol Jackson, Tape 1, June 21, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Carol Jackson, Tape 2, June 21, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Miller, Carol Jackson, Tape 1, Copy, June 21, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Carol Jackson, Tape 2, Copy, June 21, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Missing and Murdered Children Parents, "for AJC" [ Atlanta Journal Constitution]. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Morris, Aubrey, August 12, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Morris, Aubrey, Tape 2, August 12, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Patterson, Gene [Eugene], n.d. [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Pressley, Bill, November 18, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Redding, Morris, June 23, 1993 (Box CD1)
    - Royal, George, April 8, 1992 (Box CD2)
    - Scott, C.A., August 7, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Scott, Port, July 10, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Sibley, Celestine, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Sibley, James, February 1993 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Sitton, Claude, April 23, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Smith, Ed, April 22, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Spalding, Hughes, Jr., February 1993 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Sullivan [Challenor], Herschelle, January 19, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Sweat, Dan, September 23, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Sweat, Dan, November 7, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Sweat, Dan, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Talmadge, Herman, December 3, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Talmadge, Herman, August 18, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Talmadge, Herman, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Thompson, Amanda Allen and Knox, December 14, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Thompson, Robert, August 24, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Tuttle, Elbert, n.d. [Transcript available] (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Watson, Jack, Jr., October 7, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Young, Andy, May 1992 [digitized; filename 3666] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Young, Andy, July 24, 1995 [Transcript available] [digitized; filename 3667] (Box -, Folder -)
  - Videotapes, Subseries 4.2; Box 26
    - "Ivan Allen, Emory Journalism [Program]," October 13, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - "Maynard Jackson, Emory Journalism [Program]," November 3, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)